in this video you'll go to some examples
在此视频中，您将转到有关多个继承针固定性的一些示例
of multiple inheritance pin solidity for
the first example we will consider the
在第一个示例中，我们将考虑合同c继承自的情况
case where a contract c inherits from
contract a and contract B here we have
合同a和合同B在这里，我们有三个合同合同a合同B
three contracts contract a contract B
and contract C for a contract C to
以及合同C，以使合同C继承合同a和合同B
inherit both contract a and contract B
we first start with the keyword a's
我们首先以关键字a开头，后跟合约名称，因此
followed by the name of the contract so
contract a comma and then V and if
收缩一个逗号，然后收缩V，如果contact包含一个称为foo的函数，
contact a has a function called foo and
contract B as a function called Bar
合约B作为称为Bar合约的函数具有合约foo和foo
contract C has both functions foo and
bar you can verify this for yourself by
栏，您可以通过编译合同和部署来自己验证
compiling the contracts and deploying
contract C
合同C，如果父母双方相同
and if both the parents had the same
function function food then contract see
功能功能食物然后收缩在这里只看到功能之一
in here only one of the functions so
which function food that contract see
哪些功能可以让您看清合约和发丝，让我们找出来
and hair let's find out
go ahead and compile and redeploy the
继续编译并重新部署合同
contract
when you execute the function foo you'll
当您执行函数foo时，当我们调用
get the string be back when we call the
function food inside contract see the
合同中的函数food参见合同B中的函数foo是
function foo inside contract B was
called and it returned the string B if
调用，并且如果您反转继承并重新部署，它将返回字符串B
you reverse the inheritance and redeploy
the contract and execute the function
合同并执行功能foo yo，将字符串取回，所以现在
foo yo get the string a back so now
we've seen that when the order of
我们已经看到，当继承顺序是内部的B函数食物时
inheritance was a B function food inside
contract B was called an in return the
另一方面，合约B被称为“返回”字符串B
string B on the other hand when the
order of inheritance was be a function
继承的顺序是合同a中的功能食品
food inside contract a was called in a
return the string gay you can see from
从这两个示例返回的字符串gay可以看到
these two examples that the order of
inheritance determines which function
继承决定了我们合同继承的功能，那么您应该如何
our contract inherits so how should you
order the contracts that you want to
根据以下命令订购要签订合同的合同
enter into your contract according to
the solidity documentation you have to
实体文档，您必须在订单中列出明显的合同
list apparent contracts in the order
from most baseline to most derived what
从大多数基准到大多数派生，我们所说的“最基础的”和“大多数”是什么意思
do we mean by most based like and most
derived so for example contract a is
派生的，例如合同a比合同更像
more based like than contract see
because contract a does not inherit any
因为合同a不会继承任何其他合同
other contracts
likewise contract B is more based I
同样，合同B的依据更多，我认为出租车和合同的依据更多
think on taxi and contract see is more
derived than both contract B and
比合同B和合同日都衍生，因为合同C继承了
contract day because contract C inherits
from a and B and if you had a contract D
来自a和B的合同，并且如果您拥有从a和C继承的合同D
that inherits from a and C the contract
D is more derived than C and also more
D比C更衍生，也更衍生和签订合同通知书
derived and contract a notice the order
of inheritance for contract D is from
合同D的继承权是从更多的空间到大多数衍生的空间，因为
more space like to most derived since
contract C inherits from contract a it
合同C从合同a继承，如果您继承合同c
is more derived than contract a if you
were to switch the order of inheritance
将继承的顺序从大多数派生切换到大多数基础派，例如
from most derived to most based like the
solidity compiler might earn air like
坚固的编译器可能会像这样赚钱
this
once we order our inheritance from most
一旦我们从大多数基本类型到大多数派生命令继承
base type to most derived how does
solidity determine which function to
坚固性根据坚固性确定要调用的功能
call according to the solidity
documentation when a function is called
多次定义的函数调用时的文档
that is defined multiple times in
different contracts solidity searches
不同的合同稳定性从右到左搜索功能，然后
for the function from right to left and
in a depth first manner right to left is
以深度优先的方式从右到左很容易理解，但让我们来看一下
easy to understand but let's go over a
quick example using contracts see when
使用合同的简单示例，请参见何时在内部调用函数foo
we call the function foo inside
contracts see you'll get the string B
合约看到您将获得字符串B，这是因为搜索了牢固性
back this is because solidity searched
for the function foo starting from the
对于从最右边的裤装协定开始的功能foo
rightmost pant contract which is
contract e and inside contract be a
合同e和合同内部都是发现函数foo
found the function foo
if contract B didn't have the function
如果合同B不具有函数foo，我们在内部调用函数food
foo and we call the function food inside
contract C then solidity will start from
合同C，那么稳固性将从最右边的裤子合同开始，发现
the rightmost pant contract finding that
contract B does not have the function
合约B没有功能foo next solid将搜索
foo next solidity will search for the
function food inside contract a since
合约内的功能食品，因为合约内定义了功能foo
function foo is defined inside contract
a the function foo inside contract C
合同C内的函数foo将导致合同内的函数foo
will result to the function foo inside
contract a and when we execute the
收缩a，当我们执行功能时，如果我们返回字符串，
function we get our string a back if we
were to switch the order of inheritance
切换继承顺序，使合同a是最右边的坦克
so that contract a is the rightmost tank
object then solidity will first search
对象，然后坚固性将首先在合同内搜索功能食品
for the function food inside contract
day before searching for that function
在合同E中搜索该功能的前一天，您可以在此处进行验证
in contract E and you can verify here
that the function food inside contract
接下来称为合同日内的功能食品
day was called next let's go over what
it means to search depth first here we
这意味着首先要搜索深度，我们有从D和D继承的合同D
have contract D that inherits from a and
C when we call the function foo on
C当我们在联系人D上调用函数foo时，它首先返回字符串B
contact D it returns the string B first
solidity search for the function foo
自该功能以来，在契约密钥内部进行功能性foo搜索
inside contract key since the function
foo is not defined inside contract D
在合同D实体内部未定义foo的情况下搜索了功能foo
solidity searched for the function foo
in the rightmost parent contract in this
在这种情况下最右边的父合同中
case contract
again the function food is not defined
再次，功能性食品未在接触中定义，请参见“坚固性搜索”
inside contact see so solidity searches
for the function food in the rightmost
在这种情况下，最右边的父合同中的功能食品为
parent contract in this case contract be
function food is defined inside contract
合同中定义了功能食品，因此坚固性称为此功能，并且
be so solidity calls this function and
it turns the string B and we get our
它将字符串B变成字符串，如果函数foo，我们将字符串V返回到此处
string V back here if the function foo
was not defined in contract B and the
未在合同B中定义，并且函数foo被称为合同D
function foo was called a contract D
then solidity will first search for the
然后坚固性将首先在合约D内搜索功能食物
function food inside contract D next it
will search for the function in the
在这种情况下，将在最右边的平移合约中搜索功能
rightmost pan contract in this case
contract C again the function foo is not
再次与合同C一起在合同C中未定义函数foo，因此具有坚固性
defined inside contract C so solidity
will search for that function in the
将在最右边的平移合约中搜索该功能
rightmost pan contract
in this case contract B function foo is
在这种情况下，合约B函数foo没有在合约内定义
not defined inside contract be so
solidity comes back to contract C and
坚固性回到合同C，例如平底锅中的功能
such as for the function in the pan
contract left of contract B in this case
在这种情况下，合同B的合同左，因为合同a定义了
contract a since contract a defines the
function foo this is the function that
函数foo这是被调用的函数，这是值
is being called and this is the value
that's being returned
那是返回的，所以我们已经看到房屋Liddy覆盖
so we've seen house Liddy overrides
functions that are defined multiple
接下来在不同合约中多次定义的函数
times in different contracts next let's
go over how to call functions of parent
仔细研究一下如何调用父合约的功能，但是在执行此操作之前，我要
contracts but before we do that I want
to first introduce you to feature
首先向您介绍功能不稳定（可以触发的事件）
instability called events you can fire
events inside the function and these
函数内部的事件，这些事件将被记录到
events will be recorded into the
transaction logs so how is it useful to
交易日志，所以对我们现在有什么用，对我们的跟踪很有用
us now it will be useful for us to trace
function calls I'll make another video
函数调用我将制作另一个有关事件主题的视频
for the topic of events where we will
explore in more details for now I'll
现在详细探讨，我将向您展示如何声明事件
just show you how to declare an event
file your event inside the function and
在函数中归档事件以及如何在事务中查看事件
how to see event inside the transaction
log you can define an event by starting
日志中，您可以通过以下方式定义事件：以关键字event开头，然后以
with the keyword event followed by the
name of event that you want to define in
在这种情况下，您想要定义的事件的名称我将其命名为nog
this case I'll just name it nog inside
the event you can pass parameters that
如果您可以传递您现在要登录的参数，那么真实的狗
you want to log in nowadays real dog the
name of the function by passing it as a
通过将其作为字符串传递给您可以触发的函数内部的函数名称
string inside the function you can fire
the event by starting with the keyword
该事件以关键字email开头，后跟事件名称
email followed by the name of the event
that you want to fire and passing in the
您想要触发并传递您想要的参数
parameters that you want along
compile and deploy contract day and then
编译并部署合同日，然后执行功能foo，然后单击
execute the function foo click on the
transaction dog and scroll down on the
交易狗并向下滚动狗，您可以看到该事件名为
dogs you can see that the event named
dog was fired with the message a dot foo
狗被解雇了一个消息，点号为foo
was called
and that's all you need to know about
这就是您现在需要了解的所有事件，所以现在让我们回到
events for now so now let's go back to
the topic of how to call parent
可以调用父合约的主题可以称为父合约
contracts parent contracts can be called
directly or by using the keyword super
直接或通过使用关键字super通过使用关键字super
by using the keyword super all of the
parent contracts will be called let's go
父合同将被称为让我们来看一个使用实际代码的示例
through an example using actual code
here we have contract II that inherits
在这里，我们有从合同a和合同继承的合同II
from contract a and contract see also n
heads from contract a and contact e
合同a的负责人和联系人e从B和C继承而来
inherits from both B and C next both
contract B and C overrides the function
当我们调用合约B和C时，合约B和C会覆盖合约a中的函数foo
foo from contract a when we call the
function foo on contact E we want to be
联系E上的函数foo，我们希望能够看到哪些父函数是
able to see which parent functions were
called so we'll fire any bank before
打电话给我们，所以我们会在调用母合同之前解雇任何银行
calling the parent contract
compile and deploy contract D and
编译和部署合同D并在内部执行功能食物
execute the function food inside
contract D
合同D
click on the transaction and scroll down
点击交易并向下滚动到您在交易模式下的日志
to logs inside the transaction mode you
can see the C dot foo was called and
可以看到C点foo被调用，然后点foo被调用，所以当我们
then a dot foo was called so when we
call the function foo on contract D it
在合同D上调用函数foo在合同C内调用函数food
called a function food inside contract C
and fighter this event next called the
和战斗机此事件接下来在合同a上调用函数foo，并且此
function foo on contract a and this
event was fired next let's see how the
接下来触发事件，让我们看看使用时如何调用pan函数
pan functions will be called when we use
the keyword super first we'll create a
关键字super首先，我们将在合约a和中创建一个名为bar的函数。
function named bar in contract a and
then we'll override the function and
然后我们将覆盖该功能并收缩B和C
contract B and C
the function bar inside both contract B
合约B和C内的功能栏首先发出一个事件，紧接着原因
and C first emits an event next to cause
the pan contract by using the keyword
使用关键字super进行平移合约让我们看看将要发生的事件
super let's see which events will be
fired when we call the function bar on
当我们在合同D上调用功能栏时重新触发并重新部署时触发
contract D recompile and redeploy
contract D
合同D
execute the function bar and scroll down
执行功能栏并向下滚动并单击交易
and click on the transaction
you can see in the transaction logs that
您可以在交易日志中看到该栏先被称为下一个B
see that bar was called first next B
that bar was called and finally a dot
该条被调用，最后一个点条被调用，所以当我们执行
bar was called so when we executed the
function bar on contract D it first
合同D上的功能栏它首先称为合同内的功能栏
called the function bar inside contract
C next instead of calling the pan
C接下来而不是先调用pan合同，而是先调用函数
contract it first called the function
bar inside contract D and finally it
合约D内的功能条，最后它称为合约内的功能条
called the function bar inside contract
a notice that super dive bar was called
超级潜水栏被两次调用但在事务日志中的通知
twice but inside the transaction log
data bar was emitted only once
数据条仅发射一次
in summary you can explicitly call the
总之，您可以显式调用父合约或使用关键字super
parent contract or use the keyword super
to call all parent contracts
调用所有母合同
in this video we went over how to write
在本视频中，我们讨论了当我们
multiple inheritance in solidity when we
this two inheritance
这两个继承顺序很重要，您需要
ordering is important and you need to
this Japan contracts from most base type
这个日本合同从大多数基本类型到大多数派生类型，有两种方法可以
to most derived there are two ways to
call parent contracts you can explicitly
调用父合约您可以显式调用父合约的功能
call the function of a parent contract
or use the keyword super in this case
或在这种情况下使用关键字“超级”，则所有即时平移合约都将是
all immediate pan contracts will be
called thank you so much for watching if
打电话非常感谢您的观看，如果有什么不清楚的地方，请把您的
anything was unclear please put your
questions in the comments below have a
下方评论中的问题度过了愉快的一周，下周再见
nice week and I'll see you in the next
video
视频